♪ ♪
This is B. Bob, your WBW traffic
eye in the sky, and it's a
glorious Atlanta morning,
much too nice to go to work.
So far, the thruways
are flowing smoothly,
but there will be tie-ups
due to construction
later in the morning.
So, for those of you
still in bed, good luck.
Now, back to WBW's own
Arthur "Say It Like It Is" Saxon,
the man you love to hate.
WBW Arthur Saxon. Talk to me.
Hi, Arthur, it's Gloria.
Gloria.
Well, I should've
know it was garbage
by the sound of seagulls.
What's on your alleged mind
this morning, sweet cheeks?
The way you're always
bad-mouthing Robby Moore.
Moi? Mo-ee?
Bad-mouth Moore the moron?
Good... morning, Atlanta!
Get up!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
It's Robby Moore.
Moore... Moore.
Oh, come on, I think
he's kind of cute.
You do? Well, I used to work
with him right here at WBW.
And I think he's adorable.
I love the way he got
Diedre Wallace cancelled.
He could be top disc jockey.
How many of you actually
know somebody named Bambi?
Come on now, raise your hands.
No, no, no, no,
not both of them!
I admire the way he fired
Leonard Gilbert, the only man
who would take him on as
manager when he was nobody.
I had the worst meal
of my life last night.
Now, I would be a good guy
and tell you what the
name of this restaurant it,
but the only thing is, they
buy airtime here at old WZF.
And as Bambi once said,
"Hey, I'll do anything for a buck."
"And I worship, worship the way
he shafted our own
station owner, Marty Lynch,
by jumping ship to
our chief competitor
after Marty made him a star.
Yeah, real class act,
that rowdy moron.
Folks, this is Robby
Moore reminding
you that if your
child is threatening,
"I'm leaving home,"
please get it in writing.
Get them out of the house.
I'll tell y'all a little story,
you know, last night,
I went out with
this really nice girl,
sweet, sensitive, smart... what a
bummer. Speaking of lungs, ooh!
Ah! Ah! She didn't
smoke, didn't drink,
didn't even have a tattoo... disgusting!
Have you seen this new billboard...?
Well, you can't win them all. The
only problem with the war on poverty
is, they didn't shoot enough
poor putzes like you, ding-dong.
Talk about your Silicon Valley.
You're on with Saxon.
Say Arthur, do you
know the Communists
have taken over the
entire US Senate?
No, but if you hum
a few bars, I'll fake it.
♪ Do you know the
Communists are taking over? ♪
You are on with Saxon.
Southwest and westerly
at ten miles an hour...
WBW Radio, Arthur Saxon.
Please, whoever this is, let
them have access to a brain.
Whenever you talk
about Robby Moore,
you always leave out
one important point.
Yeah? What's that?
Enlighten me, babe.
The point is, you're no longer
number one in drive time.
Robby Moore is.
WBW Radio, 98.6 FM Atlanta.
Anybody out there? Talk to me.
Well, if everybody carried
a sawed-off shotgun,
there be a lot less crime.
Yeah, and a lot fewer
people, too, dork.
Well, snapper, there ought
to be a law against you.
Yeah, well there is
a law, mush brain.
It's called freedom of speech,
and it's in the Constitution.
You're out of here.
WBW Radio, Arthur
Saxon. Talk to me.
Arthur, I read
that if you dream,
you're falling into
a vat of chocolate...
Whilst we ponder that
often-burning question.
What do you say to
God when She sneezes?
Think about it, Atlanta.
People! People! People!
It is 9:59. This is it.
I am sick of you people,
and I am out of here!
Try not to screw up too
badly until 6:00 a.m. tomorrow
when I will be back
to straighten you out.
I mean the meantime, this
is Mad-Mouth Arthur Saxon
saying, "Hey, I
am only serious."
Boom. Yeah. Bop!
Hi, this is Melanie on WBW
Radio, 98.6 FM Atlanta.
What the hell is
going on, Marty?
I've been telling you
for three weeks now
that phone link is worthless!
Get it fixed!
Arthur, I've got some bad news.
Robby Moore is dead.
He's been murdered.
So what's the bad news?
Now, your car was seen coming
out of the Moores' driveway...
What the hell? just at the time
Moore stopped broadcasting.
Oh, really?
Yeah, a witness said
it was going so fast,
he couldn't get out of the
way; sideswiped his car.
Put a crease in yours
on the right front here.
Scared the hell out of him.
I haven't been anywhere
in this car since 6:00 a.m.
Still warm.
Anybody could
have driven this car.
I keep the keys in the
glove compartment.
Oh, what am I, a magician?
I can be in two
places at one time?
For the past four hours,
I have been behind the mic,
dazzling hundreds of
thousands of listeners.
Ask Marty.
He's my biggest fan.
Has to be. He owns the station.
I had to tell him.
About the relief tape you play
when you eat breakfast.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Saxon.
Sure would appreciate it if
you'd come downtown with me.
Yeah...
Oh, it's nice.
Yeah, I like that.
Morning. Morning.
What do you think?
Ben? Nice, huh?
Ben? Huh?
A friend of mine's
been arrested.
Oh... Is it, uh, anybody I know?
No. I've been seeing him,
you know, socially,
just for a short time.
Well, what was he arrested for?
Murder.
Somebody you've
been going out with
was arrested for murder?
Ben, will you
just... Did he do it?
Oh, I can't imagine that he did.
He is such a... gentle,
kind, intelligent person.
Well, he sounds like
some kind of nice guy.
He is.
He's Arthur Saxon.
From the radio?
Yes! Oh, you'll like him, Ben.
He's, he's smart
and he's clever...
He's a genuine, true jackass!
You see, that's just an
act for his radio show.
Underneath, he's warm.
He's sensitive.
Really.
That's his job.
Once you get to
know him, he's...
I said I'd talk to him.
Yes! Arthur, hi.
Well... Yeah!
I take it you people
like each other.
What's not to like? Uh...
Uh, Arthur, this is Ben Matlock.
Ben, this is Arthur Saxon.
Is that it?
Not even "hello"?
I told him you didn't
kill Robby Moore.
Yeah, well, she told you right.
I'll go see about
the arraignment.
I didn't agree to take the case.
Why the hell not?
My money's as good
as anyone else's.
What's the matter
with you? Nothing.
I'm fine.
Police found the murder weapon.
They tell you that?
They told me they found
a .38 in the trash can
half mile from Robby
Moore's house, yeah.
Registered to you.
I collect guns.
It would be very easy
for someone to steal
a gun from my house.
You have any idea when
that might have happened?
Remember that party a
couple weeks ago, 150 people?
It was probably then.
You didn't think
much of Robby Moore.
He was slime mold.
But you didn't kill him?
This is personal. Isn't it?
You don't like me.
Not much.
And you hate my radio show.
Yeah... Well, I
call a creep a creep
and a jerk a jerk.
I don't suffer fools gladly.
Do you, Mr. Matlock?
I mean, unless it's for money.
Not even for that.
Good to meet you, Mr. Saxon.
Okay, you don't like me.
You don't like what I do.
But I say what I think
and I believe what I say.
I may be angry, but I'm honest.
That's a very nice speech.
You'd better pray you've
got a lot of nice speeches,
'cause the trouble you're in
is very serious.
The charge is
first-degree murder.
Ben, please.
Moving toward the
recommendation from both sides,
I hereby set bail for
Mr. Saxon at $150,000.
Your Honor? Pam,
I'm out of here.
- Come back here!
- Arthur!
Bailiff! Hold that man! Arthur!
Please!
Man, that judge sure
is a hard-boiled old...
Try that one more time
and I'll let you rot in jail.
What's with him?
Ben is your only hope.
All right.
What happens next?
All right, all right, I'm sorry.
Grovel, grovel... I
won't do it again.
Okay, we have to
figure out who set you up.
Now, this tape you play
while you eat breakfast,
it's called a "relief tape"?
Yeah, I tape people who
call in after the show's over
and play the tape
during my break.
Do all deejays
use a relief tape?
I'm a radio
personality, Matlock.
My name is Mr. Matlock.
Pardon moi.
Are you the only
radio personality
who uses a relief tape?
That I know of, yeah.
And who, besides you,
knew about this tape?
Well, there's three people.
They're all friends of mine.
Marty Lynch, he's
the station owner,
Diedre Wallace, she's the
deejay, used to have the show
that came on after mine,
and Leonard Gilbert, my manager.
And they all hated Robby Moore?
We'll start with them.
I'm ready.
Uh, no, that means
Ben and I will start with them.
You go on home and try to relax.
Have dinner with me?
8:00?
I'll relax.
Well, what next?
What an absolute creep!
Please, Ben, he's not a creep.
It's just that under pressure,
his radio personality
slips into real life.
He can't help it.
He's a creep.
What the matter with you?
I've never seen you
this crazy over anybody.
He's wrong for you.
I know it. I know!
What do you think, you're
going to change him?
Well, there's
always that chance.
You can't change a rattlesnake
into a pet rock you walk
around with in your pocket.
Sooner or later,
he's going to bite you.
It's probably sooner than later.
As, uh, most of you know,
I was a disc jockey at WBW
when Robby first signed on.
I'll never forget
how excited he was
the first time he sat
down in front of that mic.
Or how truly grateful he was
for any help that any one
of us could ever give him.
Just had to see for myself.
Be just like you to try
to pull a fast one on me.
Mr. Lynch? Michelle Thomas.
We had an appointment.
What happened?
Your client happened.
Arthur did this?
Yeah. Well, I told him
I was taking his show
off the air until this
murder thing blew over,
and he went nuts.
He accused me of being
the one who framed him.
Hey, wait a minute.
I-I liked Robby Moore.
I gave him his first big break.
So you didn't mind
that he took that job
with a rival station?
Actually, I hated that.
I hear he cost you close to
$600,000 in lost advertising.
Yeah, well, I hated that, too.
But I-I didn't kill him.
I was at home, and I was alone!
I've only killed Robby
Moore in my dreams.
Arthur didn't believe you.
Benj! Benj!
Benjamin!
Yo... Benj!
Hi. Hi!
Did I wake you?
No. Good!
Good. You know,
the other day I noticed
you had a leak in your sink.
About a drop a second.
You know how much water
that amounts to in a day's time?
Enough to keep an entire
Ethiopian family going. Hmm.
7:00 in the morning,
and you've already found
a way to give me guilt.
What's that?
I sent away.
$39.50.
It's the Mr. Handy Man.
I'll fix that leak.
Oh, no, that's too much
trouble. I'll call a plumber.
Bite your tongue.
20 bucks an hour?
Not while Ace Calhoun is around.
And looky here, every
wrench known to man.
Sockets, domestic and metric.
And looky here,
a spark plug
wrench for a Ferrari.
You don't own a Ferrari.
We don't know anybody
that owns a Ferrari.
Well, it sets an example
for the other tools.
Well, you know,
I do get restless
in the mornings,
what with Robby Moore gone.
I tried to listen to
that other crumb.
You know, the nasty one?
Yeah, Arthur Saxon. Yeah.
Boy, that guy really
gets under my skin.
Sometimes, I'd like to
punch him right in the kisser.
Mm-hmm.
He's a suspect, you know.
Yeah, I know.
I'm defending him.
Did a tornado come through here?
May I help you, sir?
Yeah. Is Leonard
Gilbert here yet?
This way, sir.
Um... Mr. Gilbert?
Ben Matlock.
This is your fault.
If it weren't for you,
that maniac would be
in jail where he belongs.
This suit cost 800 bucks.
Grape jelly doesn't come out.
Arthur, uh... Arthur threw
jelly on your suit?
Let me get this straight.
Arthur just walked in here
and started throwing
jelly and stuff?
That's not funny!
I'm sorry.
First, he just yelled at me.
Accused me of framing him
for Robby Moore's murder.
He didn't get
violent until I told him
I was dropping him as a client.
Oh. Oh, why-why was that?
I'm an agent, Mr. Matlock.
If a client goes down,
I go down with him.
I need Arthur like I
need a hole in the head.
Oh.
WBW just laid him off.
Ten percent of zero is zero.
Oh. So, uh...
you dropped Arthur like
Robby Moore dropped you?
He decided that
he'd outgrown me.
Accused me of stealing from him.
How? He owed me money.
That ungrateful rat.
I bought him his first suit.
Had his teeth capped.
Paid for his nose job.
Talked Marty Lynch into
giving him his first shot.
Hell, I created him!
And he just stabbed
you in the back.
Yeah.
Well, he's dead.
I'm not.
Arthur's going to fry.
Things are looking up.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah...
Things are looking up.
Yeah.
I enjoyed talking with you.
Yep. Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. Make it quick, okay?
Arthur! Security is on its way!
So just don't do
anything you might regret.
You lied to me,
Marty, didn't you?!
You said you were home
when Robby was
murdered, but you weren't.
Who says I wasn't?
Your neighbor.
Mrs. Krueger.
Said she saw you
leave your house at 7:30.
Moore was murdered at 7:45.
Oh, come on. What does she know?
The old bat's always
half in the bag.
You wasted him, then
framed me. Didn't you?
No, Arthur, please!
Don't, don't, Arthur!
That's enough, Mr. Saxon!
You are history!
I don't get it, I don't
get it, I don't get it!
You're my lawyer; you'd better
come up with something fast!
What talent did
you rip that off?
Okay, that's it!
That's it.
You'd better listen to me.
You don't have a job.
You don't have a defense.
And in about a minute,
you won't have a lawyer.
You can't quit on me now.
I will in a heartbeat.
Go ahead.
I'll survive.
And I'll come out on top.
'Cause I've got talent
and I've got guts.
And what more do I need?
I'll tell you.
You need some damn common sense!
You need a jury that
wants to find you innocent.
Not one that can't
wait to find you guilty.
It's your job to
convince the jury.
Yeah it's my job!
You keep committing
mayhem, getting arrested,
treating the whole world like
everybody's a fool but you,
that jury's gonna find you
guilty, condemn you to death,
the state's gonna
show you the chair,
the guards are
gonna strap you in it,
the chaplain is gonna
pray over your stupid head
and I'm gonna pull
the switch personally
and applaud. You got that?
Hello, Ben, Arthur.
I got the relief tape from WDW.
You played this
relief tape every day?
Right.
But not exactly
at the same time.
Well, whenever I got hungry.
Sometimes earlier,
sometimes later.
So, there was no way
any of our suspects
could've known Arthur
was playing the tape.
Unless something on the tape...
tipped one of them off.
But what would
we be listening for?
I don't know.
Aren't you gonna stay? No.
You stay.
If you hear anything
peculiar let me know.
FEMALE CALLER: What can I do?
Don't forget, sweet cheeks,
a friend in need is a
pain in the B-U-T-T.
Do unto others before
they do unto you.
Yo! This is Arthur Saxon,
lean, mean and better
than you deserve!
WBW Radio, 98.6 FM, Atlanta.
I'll rewind. No.
I, uh, I can't listen anymore.
I'm not hearing
anything important
or peculiar.
Maybe you need a break, Arthur.
I'll make some fresh coffee.
No! Throughout the show,
I've had a dozen cups already.
I'm not gonna sleep for a month!
Why don't, uh, you and I just
sit down over here and talk?
We've been talking for hours.
About the case.
You're on trial for your life,
Arthur; the case is important.
Mm-hmm.
Better?
Yeah.
Mm.
Arthur, you can't kiss me here.
All right, I'll kiss you here.
Arthur, no...
You're making me very nervous.
Since when?
The cleaning crew comes
on Wednesday night.
What time? 10:00.
Got 23 minutes.
Arthur!
You are hopeless!
What do you mean hopeless?
You're the kind of man my
mother warned me about.
A heartbreaker, love
them and leave them.
A dangerous man.
And you're my lawyer.
So, I don't want to get you mad.
I'm not mad.
You're not?
I never asked you for
a commitment, Arthur.
At least once in
every woman's life,
she should kiss a dangerous man.
Maybe you and I
should get out of here.
Go somewhere
quiet like my place.
Well, Pa, the rooster's
crowing and the sun's a-rising.
Where does the time go?
Well, Ma, when we're jawin'
with our friends at WCPG,
midnight to 6:00 is
just a spit in the wind.
So, tell me nighty-night,
this is Diedre Wallace
saying so long, ya'll.
♪ WCPG country
pickin' good time ♪
93.4 on your FM dial.
Yeah, that's pretty funny stuff.
I've been here three months,
nine days and six hours.
You sound like
you don't like it.
I used to be the top DJ at the
number one station in Atlanta.
Now, I do
commercials for tractors
and give pork belly reports.
What do you think?
Gee, on the air, you
sound like you love it.
So, I'm a great actress.
Hell, pays the rent.
Huh. Huh.
Yeah, uh... ooh!
Oh, those were all taken
when I was back at WBW.
Out here a celebrity
is the county fair winner
of the hog calling contest.
Oh.
Is there a picture of
Robby Moore up there?
No, but I don't have one of
the Ayatollah up there either.
I don't want to be rude
to you, Mr. Matlock,
but I am real beat and I
want to get out of here.
I just want to go
home and go to bed.
Is that what you do, uh, every
day after your show? Go home
and go to bed?
Exciting, isn't it?
Yeah, and that day I went
home and went to bed,
and I got up around
2:00, put on the television
and heard the news about Robby.
I just marveled to think that
there really is some
justice in this world after all.
Paul.
Where's Arthur?
Oh, at home, I hope.
Yeah, that little creep.
Thinks he can come in here
and wreck my office
and take a swing at me.
Arthur's pretty hard
to take sometimes.
Arthur's pretty hard to
take most of the time.
But I think you're gonna want
to drop your assault charge.
Ah... no, no, no.
Not on your life!
Don't think you can come
in here and lawyer-talk me
out of seeing
Arthur in jail, uh-uh.
Well, Mr. Lynch, you
lied about being home
the morning Robby
Moore was murdered.
What are you saying?
I had a talk with
Mr. James T. Crosby.
I believe you know Mr. Crosby.
Yeah, I know him.
So does your sound engineer.
He saw you having
breakfast with him
the morning of the murder.
Yeah, well, we were,
uh, talking business.
Big business.
I understand James T. is
negotiating to buy your station.
Mr. Matlock, please.
If the wrong people
find out about this, the...
That business deal can
go right down the tubes.
So, that's the secret
you were trying to protect
by saying you were at home.
Well, yeah. I mean,
wouldn't you?!
This, this deal
is worth millions!
Look, you're not gonna tell
Arthur about this, are you?
I mean, he's got a mouth
bigger than the Mississippi.
He does, doesn't he?
Arthur, I took a course
on positive thinking,
and it changed my life.
See, I used to think I was
weak and wimpy and...
Yeah, well, you
still are, toad-breath.
Take a course in skydiving
and call me from the cemetery.
Anything? Not yet.
Don't you keep a
record of who calls?
Those yo-yos? Huh.
Wait, remember you told me
that when a listener goes on the air,
the station sends an official
WBW mug with your picture on it?
Oh, so you do.
You not only have
the names of the yoyos
but their addresses.
I'll call the station.
Well, if everybody carried
a sawed-off shotgun,
there'd be a lot less crime.
Yeah, and a lot fewer
people, too, dork.
Tsk. Well, there...
There are 11 voices on that tape
and only ten mugs were sent out.
Why?
Someone could refuse a mug.
One of these 11
people refused a mug.
Which one?
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, I think I do know.
It's that old guy that calls
about twice a
month, Mr. Paranoid.
Thinks everyone should
be armed and shoot to kill.
Ha. Probably lives in a bunker
and doesn't want
anyone to know where.
Does he always refuse?
Yeah, well, I guess so.
Well, if everybody carried
a sawed-off shotgun,
there'd be a lot less crime.
Yeah, and a lot fewer
people, too, dork.
Oh, come on, man, this
is a big waste of time.
Wait, wait a minute, wait.
Well, if everybody carried
a sawed-off shotgun,
there'd be a lot less crime.
This is the person who
killed Robby Moore.
How do you know?
I just know.
I can't prove it yet.
Hmm.
Some deal, huh? Yeah.
Station built him a studio
right in his own house.
Must've wanted him
pretty badly. Yeah.
Hmm.
Pretty nice-looking
fellow, wasn't he?
Mm. You know.
Uh, you used to
be a-a disc jockey
at, uh, station WBW
along with Arthur Saxon and
Robby Moore, is that right?
Yes, I was.
But you were... let go.
Fired, Mr. Matlock, yes.
Didn't the listeners
like your program?
Robby Moore didn't like me.
He was jealous,
so he had me fired.
Oh.
But after a while, you
found another position
at station WCPG?
Voice of the Boonies, yeah.
Same pay?
Hardly.
Much less.
So much less in fact
that the, um, the bank,
uh, repossessed
the home you bought.
I lost my home, yes.
Well, with Robby Moore dead
and, uh, Arthur Saxon
out of the running,
why, uh, maybe something will
come up for you back at WBW.
Objection!
I fail to see the
relevancy of any of this.
It goes to motive, Your Honor.
Your Honor, the people have
already established motive.
Uh, for my client, yes,
but not for the person who
actually killed Robby Moore.
Am I correct in assuming
you know better than to make
an allegation without proof?
Uh, yes, ma'am, I'm
going for that now.
Proceed.
Thank you.
Uh... Uh, when you were at WBW,
did you ever, uh, send
your car out to be washed?
Yes.
How'd you do that?
I would call an attendant,
he'd take the car someplace,
have it washed
and bring it back.
Where'd he get the key?
I kept a spare in the
glove compartment.
Just like all the other people
who worked at the station?
A lot of people did
that, I believe, yes.
A witness testified that
she saw Arthur Saxon's car
racing away from
Robby Moore's house
right after the murder
had been committed.
She didn't see who was driving,
but you knew about the key.
You knew where
Arthur parked his car.
So, I submit, it was you
who was driving
the car that morning.
I was at home, sleeping.
No, I don't think so.
Well, if everybody carried
a sawed-off shotgun,
there'd be a lot less crime.
Know who that was?
I have no idea.
That's one of the voices
on the relief tape we've
heard so much about.
The one the prosecution says
that Arthur was playing
when he was not on the air.
So?
All right, what about this?
Well, Ma, when we're jawin'
with our friends at WCPG,
midnight to 6:00 is
just a spit in the wind.
That's me on WCPG.
That's hardly a secret.
No, no, the secret
is... that you are also
our shotgun-carrying
Mr. Clemens.
That's ridiculous, I am not.
You're a very, very
talented woman.
And I have a confession to make.
I'm a fan.
I listen to, on the radio,
classical music or
country and western.
I'll go from Mozart and Brahms
right to Eddy Arnold,
and I listen to you.
You're very talented.
You do all those voices.
You do them so well,
no one would ever know
that you are not all those
people except for one thing.
Where are you from originally?
Arkansas.
That's it.
Listening to you all this time,
and I just now figured it out.
It's the "R" sound.
People from Arkansas
often add a little
"R" sound to their words.
"Arkansawr."
"Sawred-off shotgun."
It's a beautiful accent,
but it's unmistakable.
And there your voice is,
on Arthur's relief tape.
Why would I call
Arthur's show, hmm?
Well, you called
him late Monday,
knowing it would be taped
and played on Tuesday morning.
So, on Tuesday morning,
you got in Arthur's car,
drove over to Robby
Moore's house,
turned on the radio and
waited till you heard your voice,
knowing that Arthur
would not be on the air live
and therefore would
not have an alibi.
And you went in the house
with the gun you had
taken from Arthur's party,
and shot your old
nemesis to death.
All right, yes, I
called Arthur's show.
I did it as a joke to
see if I could fool him,
which I did,
but that hardly means
that I killed Robby Moore.
Just one more
thing, one more thing.
I understand that you're
a big fan of John Lennon.
Yes, I am.
Did you ever meet
him personally?
Once.
Where was that?
He was on a promotional
tour of Atlanta,
and he stopped by some
of the major radio stations.
Ah.
Autograph that was on a picture.
"To all my friends at WBW,
now and forever, John."
That's a valuable photograph.
Mr. Lynch told me that he more
or less gave you that picture.
Put on your wall
behind your desk.
Since you were such a big fan,
he figured you'd
take the best care of it,
but when you were fired,
gone, the picture stayed.
I guess Robby Moore thought
it would look good
on his wall, too.
Whatever Robby
wanted, Robby got.
Hmm.
Maybe you can explain something.
Um, this, uh...
This is a publicity still
that Robby Moore sent out.
See, that's Robby
there in his studio,
and those are the
pictures on the wall.
You see the picture there?
Of John Lennon?
Yeah, now...
this is the photograph the
police took after the murder.
There's Robby... poor Robby...
And the pictures.
Picture of John Lennon's gone.
And here's why.
It's here in my hand.
The police retrieved it
from the wall behind
your desk this morning.
You wanted this picture so badly
that you took it
after you shot him.
You figured the people
at that little station
would never notice.
And you were right, they didn't.
I don't know much about rock
and roll music and don't care,
but I know that John
Lennon was a famous man.
And I noticed.
We find the
defendant not guilty.
A not guilty verdict is
entered in the record.
Court is adjourned.
So, I guess nice guys
don't always finish last, huh?
Mr. Saxon, with any luck,
I'll never see you again.
You still at it?
Oh, the faucet's fixed.
I found some ham and
cheese in your ice box,
and I thought I'd better
finish it before it goes bad.
Oh, good.
How's Arthur Saxon?
Oh, disgusting.
Did you say you
finished the sink?
Yeah, let's give her a whirl!
Okay.
All right, now.
When I turn the
water on down here,
you turn it on up there, okay?
Okay!
In five, four, three, two, one!
www.tvsubtitles.net